question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "question": "In the game &quot;Racko&quot; you may pick up ANY card from the discard pile.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals", "question": "&quot;Kamea,&quot; the Gilbertese Islander word for dog, is derived from the English phrase &quot;Come here!&quot;", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, &quot;White City: A Novel&quot;, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers", "question": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature", "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Mathematics", "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature", "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}